(Howard:)without sounding
so condescending?
(Leonard:)I can try, but your
plan has the words
"garbage bag" and
"Slim Jim" in it!
(Raj:)Hey, what's going on?
Oh.
(Leonard:)Genius here wants
to catch a bird
(Leonard:)with a garbage bag
and a Slim Jim.
(Raj:)Should have put it
in the bag first.
(Penny:)So, if you don't
mind me asking,
(Penny:)do you think you might
start dating again?
(Dr Koothrappali:)It's much too soon for that.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Why? Do you know someone?
(Penny:)No, but if things don't
work out with me and Leonard,
(Penny:)I'll give you a call.
(Penny:)Wait. How much do you talk
about Star Trek?
(Amy:)Okay, let's get this
Victorian party started.
(Amy:)I've done some research
(Amy:)about some traditional
parlor games we can play.
(Penny:)Like what?
(Amy:)Well, there's a fun one
called Ball of Wool.
(Amy:)You take a ball of wool,
(Amy:)and you put it right
in the center of the table.